hey you guys it's Shruti welcome back to
live like lovers today we are doing a
quick product review for you guys again
and before that if you are new to this
channel my name is Shruti I'm a travel
lifestyle and dance content over here if
you like it make sure that you subscribe
to my channel hit that Bell icon so you
do not miss out any of my content so
without any further Ado let's get into
this video so we all have some other
problems with our skin especially the
face area and we all face problems like
pigmentation dark spots wrinkles and
whatnot because of this pollution and
fast-paced life we do not get that much
time to really prep our skin but what if
I say that one bottle is enough for all
these problems so you're presenting
alpha or bhutin Serum by satin so if you
don't know Saturn is India's number one
Healthcare and well-being for women and
packaging looks really nice it has a
pink pastel color and if you see at the
front they have said that it has
so let's open this box
oh wow
I am really liking the bottle they have
given a glass material to the bottle it
comes with a lid or a dropper you can
save which can easily be applied on your
face it comes with a quantity of 30 ml
and if I say the major ingredients which
are used in this Serum is Alpha arbutin
and kojic acid aloe vera and hyaluronic
acid in it put in the major ingredient
which is used in this serum really
decreases the quantity of melanin
released in our skin and reduces these
skin tanning the Sunburn and the dark
spots so that's the major ingredient
which is used in this and three other
more major ingredients which are used in
this bottle is kojic acidic acid acts as
in skin brightening and it really evens
our skin and also acts as an excellent
exfoliator and it has two more major
ingredients that is aloe vera it really
calms your skin and we all know that
aloe vera acts as in hydration property
and also a hyaluronic acid which leaves
your skin on a good appearance and it
really removes the crab and the dead
skin and it is very easy to use just
Drip Drop and massage if this is what
they have said here that you just have
to take two to three drops around your
face and massage it gently and really
moisturize it after you are done with
this serum okay also it is recommended
by the doctors cherry on the cake it is
sulfate free paraben free cruelty free
and it's 100 Made in India and so the
USC of this Serum is it is non-sticky
and it's extremely lightweight on your
skin and it easily Blends in your skin
very quickly and exfoliates it in a very
excellent way so what are you waiting
for go grab your alpha or gluten serum
right away and don't forget to use my
coupon code through this website and get
a good special discount so if you really
enjoyed this video do give it a thumbs
up it really motivates me and share it
with any person who loves to pamper
their skin and who wants to order this
kind of serums and comment down below
which product review you want next so
till then keep growing keep dancing and
stay safe signing off bye
[Music]
thank you